<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COVID-19 Info</string>
    <string name="about_covid">COVID-19 is an infectious disease caused by a newly discovered coronavirus called SARS-CoV-2. COVID-19 affects different people in different ways.\n\nv1.1</string>
    <string name="sample_text"></string>
    <string name="covid_detail_one">COVID-19 is an infectious disease caused by a newly discovered coronavirus called SARS-CoV-2, and affects different people in different ways. Most people who fall sick with COVID-19 will experience mild to moderate symptoms and recover without special treatment.</string>
    <string name="covid_detail_two">The virus that causes COVID-19 is mainly transmitted through droplets generated when an infected person coughs, sneezes, or exhales. These droplets are too heavy to hang in the air, and quickly fall on floors or surfaces. \n\nYou can be infected by breathing in the virus if you are within close proximity of someone who has COVID-19, or by touching a contaminated surface and then your eyes, nose or mouth.</string>
    <string name="infected">INFECTED</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="recovered">RECOVERED</string>
    <string name="active">ACTIVE</string>
    <string name="deceased">DECEASED</string>
    <string name="choose_language">Choose Language</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="view_all">view all</string>
    <string name="know_more">To Know More About COVID -19</string>
    <string name="more_info">More Info</string>
    <string name="precautions">Precautions</string>
    <string name="how_it_spreads">HOW IT SPREADS</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn More</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="about">About App</string>
    <string name="hand_wash">Hand Wash</string>
    <string name="hand_wash_detail">Clean your hands often, either with soap and water for 20 seconds or a hand sanitizer that contains at least 60% alcohol.</string>
    <string name="stay_home">Stay Home</string>
    <string name="stay_home_detail">It is important to stay home and away from other people until it is safe to be around others.</string>
    <string name="social_distance">Social Distance</string>
    <string name="social_distance_detail">Put distance between yourself and other people (at least 2 meters).</string>
    <string name="clean_object"><![CDATA[Clean Object & Surface]]></string>
    <string name="clean_object_detail">Clean and disinfect frequently touched objects and surfaces daily.</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching">Avoid Touching</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_detail">Avoid touching your eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands.</string>
    <string name="dry_cough">Dry Cough</string>
    <string name="fever">Fever</string>
    <string name="headache">Headache</string>
    <string name="sore_throat">Sore Throat</string>
    <string name="version">v1.1</string>
    <string name="about_app">This app provides users with up-to-date information on statistics of COVID-19, globally from trusted sources such as [Johns Hopkins University, the New York Times, Worldometers, Apple reports].</string>
    <string name="developers_string">Developer: Husanboy Qodirov\nhusanboy.qodirov@outlook.com</string>
    <string name="made_possible">Made possible with: disease.sh - Open Disease Data API</string>
    <string name="link_to_learn">https://www.who.int/emergencies/diseases/novel-coronavirus-2019</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No internet connection.</string>
</resources>
